Here we have to cook it from scratch all the time.
- This is going to be fun!
So Agnes should now without help run the kiosk for a whole day and receive hundreds of customers.
At the same time, Janne should be responsible for the staff at a luxury restaurant-
-And also cooking for a large bunch booked evening guests with extremely high demands.
But one thing Janne and Agnes do not know about.
At the end of the day we will bring in a professional jury and let our challengers compete against each other.
Who is doing best?
A cutting chef in the kiosk or a sausage guy on a luxury pub?
- The news grill.
- Is that so?
And then you have made it very difficult anyway.
- Yeah
- A little bigger than the street kitchen anyway.
Nice to do away with the Swedish people later.
- Does it feel nice?
It feels good in the stomach?
- What is a sausage sausage as well?
If I sat in the shit before-
-So I think this will beat everything with horse lengths.
- As you now step in, there is no return
Linus, now this is clear
- So, there is a bit of a lot of membranes left.
- I would just show you that is right.
- Yes.
- Don't delay it now.
- Did you say not?
- Yes.
- Janne ...
- Linus?
- Agnest, now you actually have to think about here.
It's a very nice customer here.
- Oh no...
-What?
Why did this get so bad?
- Yes ... I regret.
- Yes, me with ... extremely much.
- That's not what I would have.
I would have a maradon roller.
The sausages feel half -finished haha.
- Now I think it is a meeting with the staff, because now the guests will be coming soon.
Nice, thank you very much.
Lovely, we fix it.
Thank you, thank you very much.
- I think...
- Yes, damn.
This is not okay.
- There, yes there.
Bullseye.
Like a glove in hand.
Why don't they buy pre -peeled?
Please, bling!
- Four oysters?
Yes, one without onions.
- one to tartar?
- Okay, a tartar.
- What does it say on the menu?
- The news grill.
Hello?
Oh, he hung up.
He heard it wasn't Janne.
What the hell is Mauri?
He would be my sidekick.
- Now we have run Håkan Söder, chairman of the Friends of the Tunnbrullen.
Now you should order a thin bread roll by Agnes and see if it keeps the measure.
-Welcome.
-Hello.
-What do you crave?
- I was going to take a thin bread roll
- What does it cost then?
- You usually say that you want a tight roll.
That it should hold together well.
- Yes.
- I'm not really sure.
And then she made a very strange strut, huh?
Yes, but it was almost just ketchup.
After all, it became like a children's roll a little neighbor.
But still interesting that she works as a chef
But this one ...
- All tables want creme caramel so there are eight.
- Okay.
What did he say?
We fix.
I have to have plates.
- Janne, it looks terrible.
- No no no.
- What is this?
- This...
- You, up with self -confidence.
She also has a tough time.
- Who will win?
- I'm not entirely sure.
If the sausage guy only serves as he is used from his own kiosk-
–Desa delicacies that he gets access to-
- So it should be very good anyway.
It is difficult to do something extremely interesting in a sausage kiosk maybe.
- Nice colors.
- Yes.
Welcome in...
Adib!
- What a hero you are, Adib!
- How the hell did you succeed?
Check out, check out what sexy plate.
- Walla it's fantastic!
It's really neat.
- When you talk to me ...
Your break also disappears when you talk to me.
- Are you nervous Jan?
- Yep.
I don't know what to say.
- You can imagine telling you what you have cooked anyway.
- Fried steak with fried potatoes, some fried vegetables and ...
What's the name?
- What kind of thing?
- That sauce.
- Then we release you Jan, and then the jury should eat.
- Thank you, Jan.
Thank you all.
- The sauce.
What do we say about the sauce, mayonnaise?
- It almost needed a little more, I think.
-Everything is quite dry, like the rest.
- I think it's pretty good.
It has a good acid in itself and it is resilient
Compared to a finished bea or some finished sauce it is very good.
- What I appreciate is that it is not a mayonnaise consistency.
That it is a little thinner.
- If you had stood there in the kitchen with me, you would have understood what an unlikely randomly it is.
That this mayonnaise is still approved for you.
- Or is it also the feeling that he may always cook on some kind of intuition?
- Yes ...
- You continue.
Now I see that you are sitting and pressing.
You eat the more.
Should we have a beer or?
- Get chairs.
That is why you have with Edward Blom for such proposals.
Bowl!
There we sat and drank beer and found that it is about as difficult for a sausage guy as for a star chef to change jobs.
Then Jan was introduced to the priest's little crow.
The priest's little crow would go out and go, no one had him driving.
And he slimmed here, and he slipped there, and he slipped you in the ditch.
And then he slips into the ditch!